[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0210a_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_Obelisk_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_12 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_quest_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side01_ReapersLocus_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_1a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_01_Secrets_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side02_01_Secrets_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0203a_Survivalist_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side02_02_EarthProvide_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_01_Infernal_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side03_01_Infernal_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side03_02_Belly",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0230a_Ranger_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side03_02_Belly_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side03_02_Belly_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_01_Location",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_01_Location_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_01_Location_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_01_Location_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 27,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_02_Reflection_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_02_Reflection_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0231a_Painter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side04_03_Masterpiece_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc4",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_01_Tea",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_01_Tea_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side05_01_Tea_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side05_02_Achene",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0232a_Naturalist_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side05_02_Achene_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side05_02_Achene_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_01_Bears",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_01_Bears_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side06_01_Bears_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0233a_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side06_02_PapaBear_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_01_Memories",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_01_Memories_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side07_01_Memories_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side07_02_Death",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side07_02_Death_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0234a_Mourner_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02_Quest_28",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side07_02_Death_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side07_02_Death_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_01_Treasures_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_01_Treasures_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_0249a_02_Aethelwynn",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_2a",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_02_LostReturned_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_03_Music",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_03_Music_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_03_Music_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_03_Music_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_04_Legacy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_04_Legacy_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_05_Reunion_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_05_Reunion_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc3",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "02A_Side08_06_Heart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0249a_Aethelwynn_6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "02A_SQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "02A_SQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "02A_Side08_06_Heart_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_title",
        "Description": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@02A_Side08_06_Heart_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
